RG 071:003, Department of Housing Planning Maps
Connecticut State Library
- Dept. of Community Affairs. Planning Maps, circa 1943-1980
  - Brooklyn (Box 2)
    - Slope map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 5-b
    - Street improvement plan, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 6-a
    - Street improvement plan, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 6-b
    - Existing and proposed municipal facilities map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 7-a
    - Existing and proposed municipal facilities map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 52.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 7-b
    - Proposed traffic volumes, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.25 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 8-a
    - Proposed traffic volumes, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 8-b
    - Recreation and open space plan, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 9-a
    - Recreation and open space plan, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.25 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 9-b
    - Existing traffic volumes, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 10-a
    - Existing traffic volumes, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 10-b
    - Land use map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 52.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 11-a
    - Land use map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 52.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 11-b
    - Soils map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 12-a
    - Soils map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 53 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 12-b
    - Buildable land map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.75 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 13-a
    - Buildable land map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.75 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 13-b
    - Topographic map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.75 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 14-a
    - Topographic map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 50.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 14-b
    - Proposed traffic plan, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 15-a
    - Proposed traffic plan, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 15-b
    - Population distribution, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 52.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 16-a
    - Population distribution, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 52.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 16-b
  - Chaplin (Box 3)
    - Base map street map, 1967 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.5 x 36.125 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-A
    - Base map street map, 1967 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.5 x 36.125 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      701 project: Conn.P-62
    - Topographic map, 1967 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.25 x 36.125 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-B
    - Topographic map, 1967 March 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.25 x 36.125 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Existing land use, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 47.625 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-A
    - Buildable land map, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-B
    - Buildable land map, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Population density map, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 47.75 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-C
    - Population density map, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 47.75 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Thoroughfare map, 1967 April 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 49.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-D
    - Topographic map, 1967 September 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Thoroughfare map, 1967 September 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Traffic volumes map, 1967 May 15; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.25 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-D-X
    - Traffic volumes map, 1967 May 15; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.25 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Traffic volumes map, 1967 May 15; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 48.25 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Proposed land use, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 49.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 3-A
    - Community facilities present and future, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 49.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 3-B
    - Community facilities present and future, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 49.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Proposed zoning map, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 49.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 4-B
    - Proposed zoning map, 1967 June 30; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 49.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
  - Cheshire (Box 3)
    - fragment (2 copies), undated; 11 x 8.5 in. (Box 3)
  - Columbia (Box 3)
    - Area of influence base map, 1964 February; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 58.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 3)
      701 project: Conn. P-45
  - Danbury (Box 3)
    - Cover, 1958 August; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in. (Box 3)
    - Source of information, 1958 August; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in. (Box 3)
    - List of maps, 1958 August; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in. (Box 3)
      701 project: Conn. P-7
    - Elevation, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 3)
      plan number: II-a
    - Drainage basins, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 3)
    - General pattern of limestone deposits, undated; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 3)
      plan number: II-b
    - Generalized soil types, 1958; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 2 inch = 3 miles (Box 3)
    - Comparative population trends and projections, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: II-d
    - Area traffic flow, 1955; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 3)
      plan number: II-e
    - Traffic sheds, 1958; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 3)
    - Evening newspaper circulation, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 3)
      plan number: II-f
    - Economic structure, 1956; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 3)
    - Topography, 1958; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: III-a
    - Drainage basins, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: III-b
    - Housing condition, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: IV-b & VIa
    - Population density map, 1958 April; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: V-b
    - Distribution of families, 1958 February; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
    - Adverse effects of industry on residence, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: VI-b
    - Public & semi-public school facilities, 1958 April; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: VII-a
    - Public & semi-public recreational facilities, 1958; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: VII-b
    - Fire stations, 1958 April; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: VII-c
    - General public & semi-public facilities, 1958; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
    - Water distribution system, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: VIII-a
    - Existing sources of water supply, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 1920 feet (Box 3)
    - Sanitary sewers, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: VIII-b
    - Traffic arteries & flows, 1955; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 2400 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: IX-a
    - Parking facilities, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: IX-b
    - Proposed zoning map, undated; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29.125 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: XIII-a
    - Structure, 1956; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 30 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 3)
    - Structure trends 1947-1956, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 30 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 3 miles (Box 3)
    - Toll telephone calls, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 30 x 25 in.; 1 inch = 4 miles (Box 3)
    - Evening newspaper circulation, 1957; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 30 x 25 in.; 1 inch = 4 miles (Box 3)
    - Flood control, undated; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 25 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 600 feet (Box 3)
    - Traffic 1955, undated; 23 x 22.5 in. (Box 3)
    - Traffic 1975, undated; 23 x 22.5 in. (Box 3)
    - Traffic sheds, undated; 23 x 22.5 in. (Box 3)
    - Key to schemes, undated; 24 x 22.5 in. (Box 3)
    - Scheme B, undated; 25 x 22.5 in. (Box 3)
    - Scheme C, undated; 26 x 22.5 in. (Box 3)
    - Scheme E, undated; 27 x 22.5 in. (Box 3)
    - Community development program - location plan, 1977 March; TPA Services; 28 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 3)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 29 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 30 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 31 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 32 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 3)
    - Base map, undated; Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 33 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 3)
  - Danielson (Box 3)
    - Base map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 34 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
      701 project: Conn. P-41
    - Base map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 35 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Existing land use, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 36 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Existing land use, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 37 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Soil types map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 38 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Neighborhood map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 39 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Topographic map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 40 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Street and traffic plan, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 41 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Sanitary sewer plan, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 42 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Sanitary sewer plan, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 43 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Storm sewer plan, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 44 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Storm sewer plan, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 45 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Population distribution map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 46 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Population distribution map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 47 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Community facilities plan, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 48 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Community facilities plan, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 49 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Land use plan, 1965 April; Raymond & May Associates; 50 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Land use plan, 1965 April; Raymond & May Associates; 51 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Central business district base map, 1963 August; Raymond & May Associates; 52 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 3)
    - Central business district base map, 1964 August; Raymond & May Associates; 53 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 3)
    - Central business district base map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 54 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 3)
    - Central business district base map, undated; Raymond & May Associates; 55 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Locality map, undated; 56 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 3)
    - Airport plan, 1960 July 20; R. Carrie; 57 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
    - Memorandums, 1964 March 25-1965 March 25 (Box 3)
  - Derby (Box 3)
    - Population distribution and neighborhood estimates, 1957 July; T.T. McCrosky; 36.75 x 30.5 in.; 1 inch = 1250 feet (Box 3)
    - Areas served by utilities, 1958 May 15; T.T. McCrosky; 36.5 x 27.75 in.; 1 inch = 1250 feet (Box 3)
    - Physical characteristics map, undated; T.T. McCrosky; 40.125 x 22 in.; 1 inch = 1250 feet (Box 3)
    - Land use and circulation map, 1974 February 15; Bryan & Panico, Inc.; 77.75 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: Map B
    - Project improvements, 1974 February 15; Bryan & Panico, Inc.; 77.75 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: Map C
    - Boundaries, 1974 February 15; Bryan & Panico, Inc.; 38.75 x 21.5 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: Map A
    - Land use and circulation plan, 1974 February 15; Bryan & Panico, Inc.; 38.75 x 21.5 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
    - Land use and circulation plan, 1974 February 15; Bryan & Panico, Inc.; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
    - Land acquistion, 1974 February 15; Bryan & Panico, Inc.; 39 x 21.75 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: Map D
    - Existing zoning, 1974 February 15; Bryan & Panico, Inc.; 39 x 21.75 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: Map 4
    - Proposed zoning, 1974 February 15; Bryan & Panico, Inc.; 39 x 21.75 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: Map 5
    - Soils map, 1973 April; Goodkind & O'Dea, Inc.; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 3)
    - Site grading plan, 1973 September; Goodkind & O'Dea, Inc.; 76 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 3)
  - East Granby (Box 3)
    - Flooded area, 1955 September 26; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 0-81
    - Grandbrook park, 1955 October 10; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in.; 1 inch = 80 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 0-83
    - Grandbrook park, 1955 October 12; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in.; 1 inch = 80 feet (Box 3)
      plan number: 0-84
    - Altitude, percentage of slopes, surface water run-off averages, 1955 November; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-01
    - Climate, 1955 November; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-02
    - Plan of development, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.75 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-03
    - Population, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-05
    - Population, 1955 November; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.75 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-06
    - Population, 1955 November; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-07
    - Population, 1955 November; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.75 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-08
    - Population, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-09
    - Plan of development, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-12
    - Super highway projects, highway system, railroad system, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-16
    - Long distance bus lines, local bus lines, railroad freight maxima, 1955 November; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-17
    - Gas: franchise & distribution, planning and zoning, traffic flow, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-20
    - Motor vehicle registration, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-21
    - Traffic accidents, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-22
    - Education, 1956 January; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-26
    - Agriculture, retail trade, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-31
    - Employment, 1955 December; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-36
    - Built-up area Hartford County, 1956 June 1; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 37.5 x 36 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-40
    - Agriculture used land, 1956 June 1; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 37.5 x 36 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-41
    - Open land, 1956 June 1; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 37.5 x 36 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-42
    - Wooded land, 1956 June 1; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 37.5 x 36 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-43
    - State parks and forests, 1956 June 1; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 37.5 x 36 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-44
    - Connecticut economic data, 1955 October; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 33.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-51
    - Manufacturing 1, 1956 June 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-52
    - Highway condition, 1957 June 11; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32.25 x 35.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-70
    - Town roads, 1956 June 30; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-71
    - Relation between state grants and town roads, 1956 June 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-72
    - Manufacturing 2, 1956 June 30; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 1-81
    - Topography, 1955 October; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-01
    - Soil characteristics 1, 1956 July 21; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-04
    - Soil characteristics 2, 1956 July 21; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-05
    - Drainage, 1956 July 21; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 36 x 29.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-09
    - Street map, 1955 October; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.5 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-21
    - Street map, 1955 October; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32.25 x 35.25 in. (Box 3)
    - Land classes 1, 1956 September 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32.25 x 35.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-30
    - Land classes 2, 1956 September 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates (Box 3)
      plan number: 2-31
    - Buildable land, 1956 March; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 4-40
    - Conditionally buildable land, 1956 March; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35.25 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 4-41
    - Maximum school population present status population ceiling, 1956 March 16; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35 in. (Box 3)
    - Maximum school population after adoption of subdivision regulation, 1956 March 14; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35 in. (Box 3)
    - Maximum school population after adoption of subdivision & zoning regulation, 1956 March 17; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35 in. (Box 3)
    - Buildability general plan element 2, 1956 June 10; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35 in. (Box 3)
    - Circulation plan general plan element 4, 1956 June 12; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35 in. (Box 3)
    - Town utilities general plan element 5, 1956 June 14; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35 in. (Box 3)
    - Subdivision condition map, 1956 March; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 35 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 8-01
    - Subdivisions street cross-sections drainage facilities, 1956 March 2; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 20.75 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 8-05
    - Subdivision requirements and floor area relations for new business units, 1956 March 4; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 20.75 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 8-07
    - Subdivisions model layout, 1956 March 7; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 20.75 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 8-08
    - Subdivision street designs, 1956 March 3; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 20.75 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 8-09
    - Highway classification and basic design standards, 1956 march 6; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32 x 20.75 in. (Box 3)
      plan number: 8-10
    - Planning program chart 1955-57, 1955-1957; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates (Box 3)
    - New town center, 1957 June; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 47.75 x 36.75 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 3)
  - East Haddam (Box 4)
    - Base map, 1966 February; Raymond & May Associates; 46.75 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
      701 project: Conn. P-60
    - Base map, 1966 February; Raymond & May Associates; 46.75 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Business district, 1967 April; Raymond & May Associates; 27.5 x 19.375 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Business district, 1967 April; Raymond & May Associates; 27.5 x 19.375 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Neighborhood plan, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 30.25 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Neighborhood plan, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 30.25 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 4)
    - Land use plan, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.25 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Land use plan, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.25 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Existing land use map, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.25 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Existing land use map, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.25 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Topography map, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.25 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Topography map, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.25 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)
    - Street and traffic circulation, 1967 June; Raymond & May Associates; 42.25 x 46.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 4)